[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Are they potentially connecting the two?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "They might be, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Do we know how radicalized she may have been herself throughout the last two, three years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Piers, we really don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last two"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you go with Eric Holder on this or do you think there is cause for concern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric Holder"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "What do you read into these two connections that may have been established?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Yes, so I think those are both very significant and the problem is right now we're dependent on Russian intelligence authorities for these stories right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "How important do you think it will be to them that something is found eventually?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Well, I think it could help people to have an ease with being able to have a resting place for their loved one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Isn't he entitled to the very constitutional rights that you hold so dear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "It depends on if you're pledging allegiance to a terrorist organization and you're working with foreign terrorists and around the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Why would you find that so hard to believe when you've had home-grown terrorists who have done exactly that, who have exactly done what you just described?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "But this is what we've seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["July"]}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Why was that logic of your argument on guns not applying here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "This is not the fourth of July where I throw a bottle rocket at you and you throw one back and we're playing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Is there an argument that there should be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, of course, there's always the right of the people to amend the constitution.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "How will it play out, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Well, there are a lot of issues there that are going to be very, very controversial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MasterCard"]}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "That means you're not his employer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Their argument is that we're like a Visa or MasterCard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'75"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "-NONE-", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "-NONE-", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "And will he be feeling that, too, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, I think for me, I left my country so I could be who I was in '75, and I didn't come out until '81 because I really couldn't be public about my sexuality because that would have disqualified me from, perhaps, being a U.S. citizen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]